{"rounds": [{"answers": [{"ans": "PANTS", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "EARS", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "VOICE", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "GLOVES", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "MINNIE MOUSE", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "FACE", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name something specific about Mickey Mouse that other mice might make fun of"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "MONEY", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BUNNY", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SUNNY", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "FUNNY", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BALONEY", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "RUNNY", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a word that rhymes with 'Honey'"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "POTATO CHIP", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "CHOCOLATE CHIP", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "MEMORY CHIP", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "MICRO CHIP", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BANANA CHIP", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BLUE CHIP", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a Kind of Chip"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "FOOTBALL", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BASKETBALL", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "CRICKET", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "VOLLEYBALL", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "TENNIS", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BASEBALL", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a sport played with a ball"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "TV REMOTE", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SOCKS", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "KEYS", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "RUBBER BANDS", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "HAIRBANDS", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "MONEY", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a common item that mysteriously disappears in your household"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "MONKEY", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SQUIRREL", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "KOALA", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SLOTH", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "WOODPECKER", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "CROW", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name an Animal that might live in a tree"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "MONOPOLY", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "CHESS", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "BUSINESS", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "LIFE", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "LUDO", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SNAKES AND LADDERS", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a Board Game that takes a long time to play"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "GUITAR", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "PIANO", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SITAR", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "VIOLIN", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "FLUTE", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SAXOPHONE", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a Musical Instrument"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "MAHARASHTRA", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "KERALA", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "GOA", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "UTTAR PRADESH", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "KARNATAKA", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "ANDHRA PRADESH", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name an Indian state"}, {"answers": [{"ans": "AMITABH BACHCHAN", "pnt": 10, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SHAH RUKH KHAN", "pnt": 8, "trig": false}, {"ans": "RAJ KAPOOR", "pnt": 6, "trig": false}, {"ans": "DILIP KUMAR", "pnt": 4, "trig": false}, {"ans": "SALMAN KHAN", "pnt": 2, "trig": false}, {"ans": "AAMIR KHAN", "pnt": 1, "trig": false}], "multiply": 1, "question": "Name a legendary Bollywood actor"}]}